知道我是如何想出 极限特工这个计划
You know how I came up with the idea for the Triple-X program?
滑板和泳池
Skateboards and swimming pools.
(奥古斯·吉本斯 极限特工创办人)
(凭一己之力终结了第三次世界大战)
滑板动作曾被局限在地面上 是属于青少年的交通工具
Skateboards used to be stuck on the ground. Adolescent transportation.
但在1977年改革了
Then 1977 happens.
南加州遭遇了特大旱灾
Big drought hits Southern California.
灾情之重 连那些有钱佬别墅的泳池都没有水
Got so bad, rich suburbanites couldn't afford to fill their swimming pools.
在这时候 有个小子灵机一动…
That's when the light clicked on. Some kid figured out
他想到自己可以在 空荡荡的泳池里用滑板半空跳跃
he could skate those empty pools and get some real nasty air.
你有看过电影 《狗镇和滑板少年》
Dogtown and Z-Boys. You ever seen it? It's a movie.
无所谓
Doesn't matter.
反正我们这位英雄 开始在滑板上…
Anyhow, our hero starts doing things on a board
做出各种 没人见识过的花招
that no one's ever seen before.
那是这世界上 意想不到的事
Things the world thought were impossible.
对那小子而言 干旱来的正是时候
Now, that kid needed that drought.
这世界也急需 那些空荡荡的泳池
The world needed those empty pools.
极限特工便诞生了
That's why Triple-X.
(小内马尔 极限特工积极招聘者)
(擅长脚下功夫的天才 20岁时已射进100个龙门)
(他以为是被复仇者联盟征召)
你今天比昨天感觉更有安全感吗 我倒不觉得如此
Do you feel safer today than you felt yesterday? I know I don't.
美军是这世上 最雄伟以及昂贵的军队…
The biggest, most expensive military in the world,
我们却被恐怖份子 惹得不得安宁
and we're still scared of shoe and tighty-whitey bombs at the airport.
为何会如此
Why is that?
因为士兵是训练来 服从命令和抗战
Because soldiers are built to take orders and fight wars.
但是 朋友 我们面临的并非战争
But we, my friend, are not at war.
我们面对的是恐怖威胁
We are at peril.
极限特工便诞生了
That's why Triple-X.
怎么了 你在节食 你不饿
What's the matter? You on a diet? You ain't hungry?
现在是早晨7点半
It's 7:30 in the morning.
那又如何 在世界的某处 已是午餐或晚餐时间了 吃吧
So? It's lunch or dinnertime somewhere in the world. Come on, eat up!
你知道谁才感觉到安全 手握公权者
You know who does feel safe? The men in charge. The world beaters.
掌握着权力的有钱人
The top-shelf, par excellence ayatollahs with all the dollahs.
因为那些混蛋 自以为合乎正道…
And that's because those righteous bastards, somewhere along the way,
与魔鬼做了交易 他们以自由来交换安全…
made a deal with the devil. They traded liberty for safety. And us,
而我们人民…
we the people,
却赔上了自由和安全 极限特工便诞生了
ended up losing both. That's why Triple-X.
正当大家还被 局限在地面时…
While everybody else is stuck on the ground,
我们已经在秀出各种 前所未闻的滑板花招
we're doing shit on the board nobody's ever even seen before.
这就是我的推销策略
Well, that's my pitch.
我当间谍远胜于 当个销售员
I always was a better spy than a salesman.
所以…你意下如何
So, what do you say?
我不是英雄 我只是一名足球员
I'm not a hero. I'm just a footballer.
那是我搞错了
My bad.
我不妨碍你了
So, Ill leave you be, then.
谁说这世上没有 免费的…一餐
Who said there's no such thing as a free meal?
全都趴下 把钱交出来
Down on the ground, now! Give me the money!
别动
Don't move! Hurry up!
动作快
Hurry up!
射进龙门
Goal!
你还说自己不是英雄
And you say you're no hero.
那真是一派胡言
I got to call bullshit on that!
你正是这世界需要 的英雄人物
You're exactly the kind of hero the world needs.
一切事物总归来说 还是围绕着同一个问题…
At the end of the day, it comes down to the same question
我在二十年以来 每个周五晚上都会问我太太
I've been asking my wife every Friday night for the last 20 years.
你想要亲热吗
Do you want some of this?
还是想要…
Or are you just gonna...
《极限特工3：终极回归》
(纽约市 中央情报局总部)
批准
Access granted.
请坐
Okay, you may sit.
各位…
Gentlemen,
这套仪器搞垮了卫星 也杀死了吉本斯
this is the device that crashed the satellite and killed Gibbons.
实验室内的知识份子 称这为"潘多拉魔盒"
Nerds in the lab have coined it "Pandora's Box.!!
我的团队回溯出 卫星最后信号来自迈阿密
My team backtracked the satellite's last signal input to Miami.
在丽思卡尔顿顶层公寓享乐的某位混蛋
Some asshole living the high life at the Ritz-Carlton penthouse
以为他可以只手遮天
thought he could hold the world ransom.
三颗眩晕手榴弹 两颗子弹 以及一个尸体袋后…
Three flashbangs, two bullets, and one body bag later,
我们接管了这套仪器
we took custody of the device.
我们设下了上百个 合适的冗余…
We must have over 100 redundancies in place
防止任何持有笔记本电脑 的骇客劫持卫星
to prevent some punk with a laptop from hijacking satellites.
潘多拉魔盒却能 轻易绕过所有防守设施
And Pandora's Box can bypass all of them.
只要按下按钮 就能轻易窃听保密通信…
With the push of a button, it can eavesdrop on secure communications,
损坏军事软件 传输虚假智能情报…
corrupt military software, transmit false intelligence, or
或是像该死的核武器 从天空中撞出一颗卫星
crash a satellite out of the sky like a goddamn tactical warhead.
这仪器一定 出自你们其中一人
One of you is behind this.
我在查出之前 誓不罢休
And I am not leaving here until I find out who.
你用书本来攻击我
You fight me with a book?
来吧 兄弟 第一章
Here you go, brother. Chapter one!
第一页
Page one!
世事难料
Shit happens.
你迟到了
You're late!
时间刚刚好 老板
Just in time, boss.
他们闯进来 掐着我们的脖子…
They bust in here, step on our throats,
盗走了足以毁灭世界 的单一仪器
and take the one device that can cause a global power shift.
我们要如何取回来
So, how do we get it back?
那班混蛋轻而易举地 击败了我们的精英部队
These assholes just took out the best of the best like it was Sunday brunch.
我们需要一个与他们 势均力敌的间谍
We need someone who can move like them, fight like them.
这个人能够与龙卷风 正面交锋…
We need someone who can walk into a tornado,
并将其当作 万分温和的微风
and come out the other side like it was a damn gentle breeze.
你认识这般人物吗
You know someone like that?
不认识
No.
吉本斯却认识
But Gibbons did.
(第一级战备等级)
–你在做什么 –那太疯狂了
- What you doing? - ThaVs loco, chico!
桑德
Xander!
嘿 朋友…
Hey friend...
等等我
give me a second.
球赛开始
And here we go, we are undeiway!
桑德 我就知道你能办到 你把世界带给了我们
Xander! I knew you would do it, Xander. You brought the world to us.
世界这么大
The world is big,
但你可以把它放在心中
but always fits in your heart.
你要永远放眼世界
Take it with you always
快去看球赛吧
Go, go, go.
桑德·凯奇大可以 像个普通人一样…
Of course, Xander Cage can't pay the satellite company,
付费给卫星公司
just like a regularguy.
什么
What?
让那些亿万富翁 更加有钱
And line the pockets of some boardroom billionaires?
你是知道的…
You know,
人一旦变得平凡 就不再特别了
these days, a regular guy can't afford to be regular.
我们走吧
Let's go.
(第一守则 不要滑倒)
(多米尼加共和国 圣多明哥)
这世界变小了
World getting smaller?
我知道这感受
I know the feeling.
逃避问题是解决不了 任何事的
Running from your problems never works out.
你需要一套新的计划
You need a new plan.
我需要的是一份新的地图
I need a new map.
别说我没警告你
Don't say I didn't warn you.
不是吧
Oh, boy.
又来了
Here we go again.
别动 混蛋
Down! Get down! Don't move, asshole!
快跪下 你这王八蛋
On your knees now, you son of a bitch!
我是真心想妥协的 但被你搞乱了
Okay, okay. I want to comply. I really wanna comply. But you're confusing me.
"别动 混蛋"以及"跪下 王八蛋" 我该服从哪一项
"Don't move, you asshole." "On your knees, you son of a bitch.!! Which is it?
–你只有三秒钟时间 –你的做法不太有效
- You have three seconds to comply! - You're not good at this.
一
One!
二
Two!
好了
Okay!
现身吧 科学怪人
Come on out, Frankenstein!
吉本斯
Gibbons! Gibbons?
数到三 你可以出来了
Oily-oily-oxen-free.
哇 你看起来大不相同 吉本斯
You really do look different, Gibbons.
你瘦了吗
Did you lose weight?
奥古斯对你的评语…
Augustus always had such, well,
一向来都不太乐观
not exactly nice things to say about you.
你是在何时发现 这一切都是虚构的
When did you realize it was all fake?
你指的是你策划的这场闹剧
You mean the clown show?
你安排埋伏的人 戴着一副昂贵的名牌耳机
You had a guy over there wearing$1 ,000 Beats
冒牌货只需一半的价格 就能到手了
when you can buy the knockoff for half the price.
那位女士赶着去搭的巴士 两小时后才开走
Or the lady that was running to catch a bus that doesn't leave for two hours.
还有用外币 购买汽水的保安
Or the security guard over there buying a soda with foreign currency?
你知道最大的败笔是什么
You know what the kicker was?
《世界多么美好》演员的客串
Clarence from It's a Wonderful Life.
那位你安排坐在我旁边 拿着一袋炸弹的老好人
The nice old man that you had sit down next to me with the bag of bombs?
他就那么恰巧知道我会说英文
Just happened to know I spoke English.
真是令人难以预料
Go figure.
–子弹有可能是真实的 –那么防弹衣也肯定得是真的
- The bullets could've been real. - Then the body armor would've been real.
我不清楚你的意愿… 但我不喜欢被人试探
I don't know you, but... I don't like to be tested.
吉本斯一直深信你还活着 他从未放弃找寻你的下落
Gibbons never believed you were dead! Never stopped looking for you.
–他真的把你当成挚友 –那他真是个傻瓜
- Hell of a friend. - Yeah, well, the joke's on him.
–因为我们从来都不是朋友 –相信我 他此刻没机会后悔
- Cause we were never friends. - Trust me, he's not laughing.
他永远也得不到任何机会了
Nor will he ever again, for that matter.
我从未见识过如此猖狂 的攻击手法
I've never seen anything like it.
这班人手法残暴 无法无天
This group is lethal, and they don't care who or what gets in their way.
我希望你会有兴趣 加入反击队伍
I was hoping you'd be interested in headlining the next fight card.
七十英尺的横跨距离 加上九十英尺的高度
Seventy feet across, 90 feet down.
三寸厚的防盗玻璃
Three inches of security glass?
没有使用任何绳索或降落伞
No rope. No line. No chute.
他们肯定很享受这个过程
I bet they had a blast.
我们比对全世界的数据库 却得不到任何脸部辨识结果
We ran facial IDs on every database in the world. Nothing.
连超速罚单纪录也没有
Not even a match on a speeding ticket.
他们像是不存在的幽灵 但在现今的数码世界里…
They're ghosts, in a day and age where
这绝对没有可能
that kind of thing is almost impossible.
好的…
Okay,
你知道我不会为政府机构做事
you get that I don't work for suits.
我又为何要扫这班人的兴
What makes you think I'm gonna want to ruin all their fun?
好吧…
Well,
你若不为了我…
if you won't do it for me,
就当是为了吉本斯
do it for Gibbons.
你的国家需要你 凯奇先生 极限特工需要你
Your country needs you, Mr. Cage. The Triple-X program needs you.
你是时候当个爱国者了
It's time to be a patriot.
按照谁的定义
By whose definition?
我上一次表现爱国时 被判三振出局
The last time I was patriotic, I got three strikes.
只有一个人愿意 相信失败者
And there was only one man who believed in the underdog.
爱国主义已灭亡了 现在只有反叛者和暴君
Patriotism is dead. There's only rebels and tyrants now.
那你属于哪一者
So, which are you?
我是极限特工
I'm Triple-X.
欢迎归队 极限特工
Well, welcome back, Triple-X.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
–伦敦 –为何 伦敦有什么
- London. - Why? What's in London?
幽灵猎手
A ghost hunter.
或许还有我的貂皮大衣
And possibly my fur coat.
我忘了这里的景色 是如此诱人
I'd forgotten how beautiful the view is up here.
看来你找回了大衣
I see you found your coat.
你答应过帮我保管
Well, you promised to take care of it for me.
我的确遵守了承诺
And I did.
我是来找人的
So, I'm looking for someone.
我们之间何时建立了 商业关系
Since when have we had a business relationship?
我若被查到碰触电脑 会被判刑二十年
I get caught even touching a computer, my ass goes away for 20.
开价吧
Name your price.
你知道我一向公平交易
You know I'm good for it.
这类的情报是无价的
Information like this doesn't have a price.
艾尹司莉 一切都有价格
Ainsley, everything has a price.
当然 你若没把握执行…
Now, if you don't think you can pull itoff,
或是身手大不如前 我能够理解
if you lost your edge, just tell me and I'll understand.
凯奇 你知道我为何犹豫
You wanna know what it is, Cage?
为什么
What?
我曾经认为你无人能比
I used to think you were the man.
但现在…
But now,
我发现你也不过如此
I don't know, maybe I feel like you're just working for him.
别这样
Come on.
没人知道我来了这里
Nobody knows I'm here.
你知道我能保守秘密
And you know how I am about keeping secrets.
无论你怎么说 国际刑警装置了新的监听器
So you say, but Interpol's got these new listening bugs.
他们化作隐形人 高超的科技不输英国军情六处
They're practically invisible. Real M16 kind of shit.
监听器可以融入肌肤 或辅佐在手臂下…
Disappear on your skin, under your arms,
甚至隐藏在私密处…
tied around your balls like a Christmas bow.
你大可以搜身
Unwrap me, then.
你知道吗 有研究证明性爱接触…
You know, studies have proven that sexual consummation irrevocably ruins
会彻底摧毁大多数关系
nine out of 10 relationships.
幸运的是 你喜欢接受挑战
Lucky for me, you love to gamble.
当然…
Of course...
不行
not.
但我的朋友们喜欢 孤注一掷
My friends, on the other hand, adore stiff odds.
孤注一掷
Stiff odds?
我为国家所作的奉献
The things I do for my country.
这像是大海捞针
Like finding needles in a stack of needles.
你虽然在英女皇的管制下 得套上脚踝监视器…
Even though you're shackled by the Queen,
本领依旧首屈一指
you're still the best in the world.
谢谢
Thank you.
帮自己一个忙 烧了这个
Do yourself a favor. Burn this.
我打听到你在找的这班幽灵 极具危害性
The whispers I hear, these ghosts of yours are the real kind of trouble.
他们受过专业训练 幕后也有雄厚的资金
They've got training, they've got funding,
会不惜任何代价 消除阻扰他们的人
and they've got no problem running over anyone who gets in their way.
你担心我会受伤
Okay, so, you're worried that I mightget hurt?
我担心你会死
I'm worried you might get dead.
你为我的安慰担忧 令我感动
You know, I'm touched that you can imagine a world without me in it.
这世界少了我 肯定少了欢乐
It'll be a little less fun.
我要说的只有这些
That's all I'm saying.
你要找的那班幽灵 此刻正在菲律宾
Your ghosts are hanging out in the Philippines.
我早该料到他们会 躲到太平洋地带
Figures they'd go to the Pacific.
一个没有网络连接的荒野
Some jungle rave that's off the grid.
你是如何在短时间内查出的
How the hell did you find it so quickly?
卧底
Undercover work.
你把潘多拉魔盒藏在哪里
Where is it? What did you do with Pandora's Box?
在一个很安全的地方
It's in a safe place.
这不是计划的一部分
That wasn't a part of the plan.
经过这么多年 你依然对我的临时变动感到惊讶
After all these years, you're still shocked when I improvise?
不是 我们的任务是销毁它
No. But the mission was to destroy it.
看来另有计划
Turns out there's a new mission.
我是不会销毁能够 让我们达到目的工具
I'm not gonna destroy the one thing I can use to get what we want.
–全世界都在通缉我们 –让他们来找吧
- The whole world is looking for us, Xiang. - Let them come!
你只在乎棋盘里的 典当牺牲
You worry about pawn sacrifice.
我却瞄准了国王
I got my eye on the king.
这就是问题所在
That's the problem.
你遗忘了皇后的存在
You forgot the queen.
(英国 莱肯希思 皇家空军基地)
你成功消灭无政府99恐怖组织之后 吉本斯收到了一张空白支票
After your success taking down Anarchy 99, Gibbons was handed a blank check.
换句话说…
Which is the long way of saying
他替你购买了崭新的 代步工具
he got you a new ride.
凯奇 在你的死讯传出后 这世界经历了重大的提升
World went and got an upgrade since you died, Cage.
板载无人机 防空对策…
Onboard drones, anti-air countermeasures,
以及巨大容量的燃油舱 足够环球航行三遍
and fuel tanks big enough to circumnavigate the globe three times
也无需降落
without ever landing.
你可以把大衣挂在衣帽间 我担保没人敢偷
You can check your coat. I promise you, no one would dare steal it.
我不能担保貂皮大衣 不会自行溜走
I can't guarantee it won't walk off on its own.
十分钟后起飞 你们已经落后七分钟了
Wheels up in 10, boys! Which means you're already seven minutes behind.
她一向来都如此有趣 或只限于特别日子
Is she always this much fun, or just on special occasions?
难怪我们的国家 会欠下万亿美元债务
No wonder our country's in debt trillions of dollars.
你们真需要这些高端科技 来抓坏人
Do you really need all these gadgets to get the bad guys?
我们什么都不需要
We don't need any of it.
但这让逮捕过程 有趣多了
But it makes the catching a hell of a lot more fun.
桑德·凯奇 我的天啊
Xander Cage. Holy shit!
仅有一夜的独家现身 这太疯狂了
Live and in concert, one night only. This is crazy!
我参加过一场科切拉音乐节 那是枪与玫瑰乐团的复出表演…
I was at Coachella and Guns N' Roses got back together,
但远比不上这个
but this is way cooler.
我其实并没有亲身 参与音乐会…
Well, I wasn't actually there, but I, like,
但我略有所闻 知道吗
heard about it, you know?
天啊 我还在喋喋不休
I'm still talking. Oh, my God.
抱歉 这是我的坏习惯 我一开始说话…
I'm sorry, it's like a bad habit. I get started and then...
–就停不下来 无法… –呼吸
- and then I can't... - Breathe.
慢慢来 若有必要 我懂得人工呼吸
Take your time. I know mouth-to-mouth if necessary.
哇 这些肌肉是怎么一回事
Are you kidding me with those guns?
你就像是真人版的终结者
You're like the frickin' Terminator!
我指的不是第一代的终结者
And I'm not talking about the first Terminator,
而是第二代 返回来杀死他的那个
but the second Terminator that goes back to kill the first Terminator.
那个金属液态的家伙
It was the liquidy metal guy.
克利尔瑞奇探员曾与吉本斯合作过
Agent Clearidge worked closely with Gibbons.
她会提供这次计划的操作援助
She'll handle support for the operation.
我能想象你这样的男性 一定需要大量的援助
And I beta guy like you needs a lot of support.
你多重 220还是230磅
What are you? Like 220? 230?
老实回答 我的吊床只能承受250磅
Be honest. 250 is the hard max for my swing.
–别这样 –我闹着玩的
- Come on. - I'm kidding.
我没有虐恋癖 也没有安全词 其实是"金橘"
It's not like I have a safe word, or anything. It's "kumquat."
我从未想过那类形式
Never really think about it.
金橘
Kumquat.
你呢
What about you?
我的字典里没有"安全"这个词语
No. "Safe" isn't in my vocabulary.
一针见血 你不愧是桑德·凯奇
Touche, you're the Xander Cage.
无论你有任何需求 贝姬都能在一小时内达成
Anything you need, Becky can source it within the hour.
除了任何非法的药物
Except for any sort of illegal drugs.
我只需十五分钟
Those, Ill have within 15 minutes.
开玩笑的
Kidding.
但你若需要紫色大麻 绝对不要来找我
But if you need a fifty of Purple Urkle, lam notthe girl to ask.
跟我来 凯奇 我来为你介绍地勤组员
Okay, Cage, follow me. I'll introduce you to your ground team.
–谢谢你 贝姬 –没问题
- Thank you, Becky. - Of course.
金橘
Kumquat.
大只佬怪咖来了
Hey, here comes the Red Bull freak show.
桑德·凯奇 为你介绍…
Xander Cage, I want you to meet Paul...
保罗·多诺万
Donovan.
保罗·多诺万队长
Captain Paul Donovan.
我在电视上见过你
I know you. I saw you on TV!
他被总统亲自颁发勋章 那一定很酷吧
The President gave him a medal. That must have been pretty cool, right?
你们一定经历过很多 伟大的事迹
You guys must have some seriously cool stories to tell.
见识过各种场面
Must've seen a lot.
我很好奇…
I wonder,
你们当中有谁尝试过 骑着越野自行车从高空自由落体…
how many of you have ever pulled a freestyle triple backflip
另加三段后空翻 大家都试过吗
on a BMX bike before? All of you?
没有 我们不玩自行车
No. We don't play on bikes.
原来你们不玩这个
You don't play on bikes.
那你们是否有踩着滑雪板…
Any of you ever carve an R4
滑下第四级风险类别的雪山…
on a snowboard
而雪崩紧追在后
while an avalanche is on your booty?
我们是军人 不是闲人
We're soldiers, hotshot. Not slackers.
好吧 但你们所有人肯定有…
Okay, but you all
使用过标准装甲部署的 降落伞系统…
have HALO jumped over Eastern Europe
进行低空开扫高空跳嫂 对吗
using a standard-issue armor deployment parachute system. Am I right?
没有
No.
我们又没有用红牛加汽水 把自己灌醉 你这混蛋
We're not all jacked up on Mountain Dew and Red Bull, you asshole.
这人哪找来的
Where'd you find this guy?
凡事都有第一次
Well, there's a first time for everything.
你刚做了什么 真是令人无法置信
What did you just do? I can't believe this shit.
我才不用一班小丑 来保护自己
I'm not gonna have clowns watch my back.
我肯定会后悔这么问… 你相信的是谁
I know I'm gonna regret asking you this, but who would you trust?
没人知道这号码
You know, no one has this number.
近来都在忙什么
So, what are you up to these days?
我吗 我正在衡量胜算
Me? I'm evening the odds.
(阿黛尔·沃夫 最多骨折纪录保持者)
(使命召唤名称：荡妇）
(最爱电影：狮子与我)
–移动 –双手举起来
Move in, move in! Show me your hands!
到车子那处
Get on the car, now!
我抵达时已经这样了
It was like that when I got here.
(泰尼森·托奇 特技车手 车祸次数为198)
(声称自己被外星人挟持过两次)
(维持最长的一段恋情对象：他的橄榄球护齿具)
只限极限专区参与者
Nobody gets in unless you're an X-Game participant! You hear me?
那人溜进去了
That guy got through.
嘿 给我回来
Hey, get back here!
最近过得怎样
What, Nyjah?
霹雳闪电 格雷戈
Lightningbolt and Burrito.
查德 你好吗 兄弟
Chad, wassup, bro?
罗伯塔 待会见
Roberta. Ill see you later.
大家鼓掌 欢迎兜帽侠
Show him the love! Give it up for The Hood!
(尼奇“尼克斯”周 别名“兜帽侠”)
(在同一个夜晚约会过 泰勒斯·威夫特和女神卡卡)
(特长：欢乐制造者)
(哈里·欧康诺)
好 坏 极端…
The good, the bad, the extreme,
加上彻底疯狂
and the completely insane.
这才是我想要的队伍
Now, this is a team I can work with.
我简单说明
Ill make this easy for you.
这四个混蛋是坏人
These four assholes, very bad guys.
潘多拉魔盒是坏东西
Pandora's Box, very bad thing.
我们会登陆马尼拉 接着你们自行前往小岛
We'll land in Manila and you will requisition your own transportation to the island.
嘿 我们不如解决掉这 从外太空来的婊子后收工
Yo, why don't we just nuke this bitch from orbit and call it a day?
潘多拉魔盒无可取代
Pandora's Box is one of a kind.
必须完整性地取回
It needs to be recovered intact.
为何 是用来做什么的
Why? What's it do?
–脑波扰乱器 –这东西杀死了吉本斯
- Brainwave scrambler? - It killed Gibbons.
你只需知道这一点 其余都属机密
All you need to know. The rest is classified.
肯定是脑波扰乱器
Brainwave scrambler.
有闻到吗
You smell that?
是换了不同套装 但相同的胡言乱语
Smells like the same shit in a different suit.
你以为狗天生就懂得 如何抓住飞盘
You think a dog knows how to work a Frisbee?
主人一声令下… 它就必须服从
Master says, "Fetch," and the bitch listens.
你嘴里咬着飞盘 的模样一定很性感
You would look so sexy with a Frisbee in that mouth.
亲爱的 这才不是一场游戏
Sweetheart, this is not a game.
你们都属我的士兵
You are all my soldiers now.
–我是玩家 不是士兵 –我们看起来像士兵吗
- I'm not a soldier, I'm a bailer. - Do we look like soldiers?
一点也不像
Hell, no.
–我把你的士兵们都丢去东欧了 –为何独漏掉拉稀警犬
- I dropped your soldiers over Eastern Europe. - So, why did you leave Lassie behind?
这次行动由我指挥 你得听我的
This is my operation! You will listen to me.
散会
Meeting's over.
人生悲剧再多也得笑着活下去
Well, other than that, Mrs. Lincoln, how was the play?
那是超高密纤维的防弹衣
Hey, that's super-cinch body armor.
你必须把带子…
You've got to tighten the strap...
尽量收紧
...over here.
我可以的
I got this.
你以为自己是我的经纪人
What are you, my handler?
我能够胜任任何角色扮演
I'm whatever you need.
我什么都愿意尝试
I can handle anything.
我的抓力也很紧实
And I've got a tight grip.
顺道一提 我不是外勤探员
And just so you know, I am not a field agent.
我从未出过任务
I do not go out in the field. Ever.
那里才有乐趣
Now, that's where all the fun is.
是的 但我害怕有趣的事物
Yeah, fun scares me.
也害怕坏人跟枪支
People scare me. Guns scare me.
尤其是持有枪支的坏人 我一受到惊吓就无法做事
People with guns really scare me. And if I'm scared, I can't do my job.
接着就会连带害死人 大家都死光了 我还能支援谁
And if I can't do my job, then people die. And if people die, then who am I tech-supporting?
没有人
Literally no one.
但我会尽全力保护你的安全
But I will make sure to keep you safe.
那并非易事
It ain't easy to keep me safe.
是的 我最爱坏男孩了
Yeah, these bad boys are my favorite, too.
这称为外围手套 最新被研发的地面战斗武器
They're called exo-gloves. DARPA's new ground combat initiative.
气动会活塞驱动齿轮 令拳头有四倍的速度和力道
Pneumatic pistons drive the gears, quadruple the speed and power of your punches.
不要
Nope, nope.
这是多级信号干扰器
This is a multistage signal disruptor.
非常易碎
It's very, very breakable.
你能告诉我 泛美航班103在洛克比…
Can you tell me the real reason behind the crash of
真正坠机的原因
Pan Am Flight 103 over Lockerbie?
可以
Yes.
你和外星人是一伙的 对吗
You're one of them, aren't you?
当心 拳王洛基
Easy there, Rocky.
我说过这手套有着 强大的力道…
I wasn't kidding when I said there's enough force in these bad boys
足以打爆机身
to probably punch a hole through the fricking plane.
继续胡闹啊 还能出什么差错
Keep screwing around. What could possibly go wrong?
–那正是我的风格 –好的 那真是庆幸
- That is my style, though. - Yeah, good. Glad to hear it.
你知道吗 其实…
You know, actually,
你还是别碰的好…
I would rather if you didn't...
真是惊喜 你真的知道如何操作底部
That's refreshing. You actually know what you're doing down there.
没错 她也曾那样说过
Yeah. That's what she said.
(菲律宾 卡拉摩安岛)
有事吗
You need something, man?
我听说这地方 最适合让我的组员…
Well, I heard this is a perfect place to disappear for a few days
不被质问地 消失几天时间
for my crew, no questions asked.
只要价钱谈拢 我家就是你家
Mi casa es su casa, if the price is right.
好极了
Perfect. Tennyson!
泰尼森
Tennyson!
你肯定会喜欢 我有南太平洋最好的武器
You're gonna like this. I just happen to have the best hardware in the South Pacific.
拿百分之三十来交换 我们这里尚好的待客礼仪
30% off the top gets you our finest hospitality package.
三十 有包括周末陪伴的女郎 再附送两棵椰子吗
30% off the top? Do I get the girls for a weekend and two coconuts?
百分之十
10%.
10%?
你一定是瞄准了其他 无法无天的偏僻岛屿
You musVve been aiming at the other lawless, uncharted island down the block. Happens all the time.
不如这样吧 你转过身上船 滚远点
Here's what you do. You turn around, go get your boat. You can kiss my ass.
好吧 等等
Okay, hang on.
你意下如何
What do you think?
是你说的
You talked me into it!
百分之十八
18%!
你把这当成了跳蚤市场
You think this is a flea market?
你以为我们在聚集区 售卖冒牌电视机和手表
You think we're in the hood selling TVs and fake watches, or something like that?
你搞什么
What's wrong with you, man?
好吧 二十二加半
All right. Twenty-two and a half.
你要如何计算"加半"
How you gonna do "and a half"?
二十二…
Twenty-two
加半
and a half.
好吧 尽情享受派对
All right. Enjoy this party.
我喜欢你的风格 兄弟
I like your style, man.
无论如何都在船上待着
Stay on that boat, no matter what.
阿黛尔 尼克斯
Adele, Nicks!
各位 小心藏好耳机
All right, guys, keep your earbuds in.
阿黛尔 一如往常 你当我天上的眼睛
Like always, Adele, you're my eyes in the sky.
尼克斯 你来炒热气氛
Nicks, you're gonna show'em how we do it.
你行吗
You got this?
等着看吧
Just watch.
你能帮我挂在吧台后面吗
Can you keep this behind the bar for me?
要喝什么
What can I get you?
蔓越莓汁加苏打
A cranberry club soda.
来两杯吧
Make that two.
–谢谢 –不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
专注点
Stay focused.
不是吧
Really?
桑德·凯奇重出江湖
Xander Cage. Back in action.
我有离开过吗
Did I ever leave?
该死的
Shit.
发现小丑了
Spotted our clown.
比想象中简单 请大家喝一杯庆祝吧
Easier than expected. Drinks all around.
是他
That's him.
你知道什么 这是猎杀混蛋的季节
What do you know? It's douchebag hunting season.
我最喜欢的捕猎项目
My favorite.
现在还没到 要杀人的时候
It's a little early in the evening to slay someone.
- 让我来补救吧 - 来吧
- Let me fix it. - Come on.
若那般舞艺还不足以被射死 我真不知道谁该死
If Dance Dance Revolution doesn't deserve a bullet, I don't know who does.
这到底是派对还是葬礼
Is this a party or a funeral? It's a party!
无论是哪一个 今晚都会有着了火的身体
Either way, somebody's getting turnt up tonight!
我说过他擅长制造欢乐
I told you he was fun to have around.
我起初以为你是特种部队一员
At first, I thought Special Forces.
但你却布满纹身
But your ink's all wrong.
美国中央情报局
CIA?
若是他们 早就派来无人机炸死我们了
They would send in a drone, bomb us to hell.
英国军情六处
M16?
你不属于他们喜欢的低调类型
You're not the kind of subtle they prefer.
来这岛屿的人 大多都是通缉犯
You know, the men who come to this island, they're on the run.
为了躲避这世界的追击
Hiding from the world.
但你不是
But not you.
你不是来逃难的
You're not here to hide.
你为了寻人
You're looking for someone.
谁说我还没找到她
And who's to say I haven't already found her?
你这番话是想吓唬我
Was that meant to scare me?
你若配上几分颤抖 会更逼真
A little tremble would be nice.
这个嘛…
Well,
看在你只差一步就得 坡脚离开这里…
considering you're one tremble away from limping out of here...
我胜券在握
? . .I'd say I'm close enough.
你的意思是 明早不会帮我做早餐
Does this mean you're not making me breakfast in the morning?
你还差几寸距离
I'd say you're a couple inches off.
碰上僵局了
Bit of a stalemate.
只要你放下枪
Not if you drop the gun.
我不是坏人
I'm not the bad guy.
我不相信好人
I don't believe in good guys.
赛琳娜
Serena?
他是谁
Who is he?
我们才刚认识
We just met.
但相处愉快 直到被某人…
But we were getting along famously until somebody
蓄意打断
decided to interrupt.
安分点
Stick to the path.
拿去吧 亲爱的
Here, honey.
这岛屿上有众多 无名牌的坟墓
There's a lot of unmarked graves on the island.
我敢说卖你那件上衣的人 就是其中一具死尸
Ill bet whoever sold you that shirt is in one of them.
你打算嚣张多久
And how long do you intend to push your luck?
直到我到达目的
Until I get what I came for.
你的目的是什么
Which is what exactly?
最烈的酒
A damn stiff drink.
我们坦诚相见吧
So, let's be real and talk about what we all really want.
我为了那东西而来
I'm only here for that.
你们大可完好的离去 除非你想延续我们之前的调情
And in my mind, you guys could walk away nicely. Unless you want to continue our foreplay.
这般威力不该 属于任何人
Power like that doesn't belong in anyone's hands.
我不过即兴发表
Just improvising.
不是吧 手榴弹 这里是九十初年代的东欧吗
Mate, seriously? A grenade? Mate, seriously? A grenade? What is this? Eastern Europe in 1990s?
他接着会给你发传真
Next, he's gonna send you a fax.
你为了独吞那东西…
So, you're willing to kill
愿意杀人
just to keep that for yourself?
你问错问题了
That's the wrong question to ask.
要如何问才是正确的
What's the right question?
"你愿意为此死吗 "
"Are you willing to die for it?"
一颗手榴弹 三个人
One grenade, three people.
我喜欢孤注一掷
I like the odds.
两颗手榴弹 三个人
Two grenades, three people.
我爱死了这场胜算
I'm loving these odds.
你有试过流了大量的血 眼前只有一片血染
You ever bleed so much, when you open your eyes, all you see is red?
当你在每个陆地上 都战斗过…
When you have fought war on every continent...
只要你一声口令 我就让这班混蛋上西天
Come on, X, just say the word. Let me put both these assholes out to pasture.
你等待的只有死亡
...you expect death.
人的身体是脆弱不堪的
Our bodies are such fragile things.
让我来射死他
Come on. Let me shoot him.
死亡有时候会…
Death sometimes just
出其不意的发生
sneaks up on you.
我很久没玩"烫手山芋" 这游戏了
It's been a while since I played hot potato.
我躺在医院的病床上…
I'm in this hospital bed.
神志不清 出现幻觉 四周都是自己流的血
I'm barely conscious. Delirious. Drowning in my own blood.
我脑海里只听到 "就是今天了"
And all I can hear myself think is, !!Today!s the day.!!
"今天是你死亡的日子"
!!Today!s the day you die.!!
我很有感触
I'm touched.
我能要回大衣吗
Can I have my jacket, when you get a sec?
接着走来了一个男人…
Then a man comes along, tells me a story
告诉我一个关于加州干旱的故事…
about a drought in California.
其中还有滑板和泳池
About skateboards and swimming pools.
以及一个名为桑德·凯奇的男人
About a man named Xander Cage.
该死的 他是极限特工
Shit. He's Triple-X.
我听闻他死掉了
I heard he was dead.
是真的吗
Is he?
我们都是极限特工
We are all Triple-X.
只不过有不同的议程
We just have different agendas.
她想要销毁这东西
She wants to destroy it.
我想要加以利用
I'm gonna use it.
你若把这带回国家安全局 我们就玩完了
And I'll be damned if I'm gonna let you take it back to the NSA.
(机密)
派对现在开始
Now, it's a party.
老实点 老实点
Everybody, get down! Move! Move!
要出大事了
Shit's about to go down.
准备好狂欢了
You ready to have some fun?
把音乐关掉
Turn off the music!
停止
Stop it!
大家把手举起来
Everybody, hands up!
现在
Now!
趴下
On the floor!
第一个移动的人就得死
First person to move, first person to die!
我移动了
I moved.
我又移动了
I just moved again. I'm still alive.
我还活着
I am still alive.
闭嘴吧"英雄 "
Shut up, "hero"!
好的
All right.
来吧
Let's do this.
别动
Don't move!
我手上有你要的东西
Okay, I actually have what you want.
潘多拉魔盒
Pandora's Box?
就在这里
I got it right here.
但你错了
But you're wrong, though.
你若从我这里拿走 就等着死吧
You take it from me, and you die first.
接着死的会是自以为能保卫你的 列宁格勒中尉
Then Lieutenant Leningrad, who thinks he's got your back.
再来就是看守门口 叫做埃文的两位士兵
Then the two Ivans by the door.
吧台的莫斯科骡子
Moscow Mule by the bar.
最后是楼梯旁的伊戈尔
And then Igor on the stairs.
你听清楚接下来会发生的事了
See where we're going with this?
但全都无所谓
But none of that matters.
因为我说过了…
Cause like I said,
你若从我这里拿走… 就等着死吧
if you take this from me, you die first.
我不管你是生或死 都会把那东西抢走
Ill take it from you dead or alive.
你若是抓得太紧 我就切下你的手臂
And if you hold it too tight, I cut your arm off.
随你便吧
Suit yourself.
列宁格勒
Leningrad.
嗨 埃文
Hi, Ivan.
另一名埃文
Other Ivan.
再见了 莫斯科骡子
Bye-bye, Moscow Mule.
伊戈尔 你又欠我人情了 桑德
Igor. That's another one you owe me, X.
注意两指之间
Read between the lines.
泰尼森 你应该来支援我们的
Tennyson! Some back-up would be nice.
来支援我们 快啊
Some back-up would be nice! Come on, man!
桑德说过我得在船上待着
X said stay on the boat.
那是俄罗斯人入侵之前的事
That was before the goddamn Russian invasion touched down, man!
桑德说过我得在船上待着
X said stay on the boat.
你要加入游戏吗
You want to play?
这东西不属于任何人
That doesn't belong in anyone's hands.
想要的话…就来抢走
You want it, come and get it.
有必要这样做吗
Was that necessary?
这会是吉本斯的意愿
It's what Gibbons would have wanted.
桑德
X!
x.
又发生了 另一颗卫星跌落了
It happened again. Another satellite fell.
我们应该携手合作
Us working as a team.
这才是吉本斯的意愿
That's what Gibbons would've wanted.
你要加入吗
You in?
莫斯科奥林匹克体育场 发生爆炸事件
An explosion inside the Olympic Stadium rocks Moscow.
有七名员工已被证实死亡…
Seven workers are now confirmed dead,
这起毫无意义的暴力 也造成至少25位伤者
with at least 25 others injured in this senseless act of violence.
来自五角大楼的消息指出…
A source inside the Pentagon
一颗离群的卫星 已被用作武器
says a rogue satellite may have been used as a weapon.
看来潘多拉魔盒 并非机密档案
Guess this means Pandora's Box isn't exactly classified.
在刚发布的新视频中 一组匿名团体…
In a new video released just moments ago, an anonymous group
声称自己有能力把 卫星用作武器 他们道出…
is claiming to have the ability to use satellites as weapons.
"侵犯全世界市民的公民权利…"
They claim "that the violation of civil liberties "of all the citizens of the world
"是一项必须被阻止的暴行"
"is an atrocity that must be stopped."
在接下来的24小时内 禁止并拆除全世界的间谍程序…
Disable and dismantle all the world's spy programs within the next 24 hours,
否则我就亲自动手 一次引爆一颗卫星
or I will do it for you one satellite at a time.
地球此刻被 三万颗卫星环绕着
There are 30,000 satellites orbiting the Earth at this moment.
我会每24小时落下一颗卫星 直到我的要求被达成
I will drop one satellite eveiy 24 hours until my demands are met.
在莫斯科的目击证人…
Eyewitnesses in Moscow...
–这也是你计划的一部分 –当然不是
- Was this always part of your mission, too? - Of course not.
我们是吉本斯新打造的 极限特工
We were a new Triple-X team Gibbons created.
我们查出一名高级智能官员 正试图操纵卫星
We discovered a high-level intelligence officer was trying to manipulate satellites.
但还来不及 掀开他的真面目…
And even before we could unmask him,
吉本斯就遭到毒手了
Gibbons was killed.
原来你一早就知道 他们是极限特工
So, you knew they were Triple-X all along.
我需要你对这次行动 保留该有的客观感
I needed you to retain a sense of objectivity.
我不明白 潘多拉魔盒已被我销毁 为何会出现在莫斯科
I don't understand. If I destroyed Pandora's Box, what happened in Moscow?
我若没猜错的话…
If I'm right, which I am,
潘多拉魔盒只能 操控一颗卫星…
this box only ever had the ability to control one satellite.
那是什么意思
What does that mean?
我们追击的 不过是一个样板
It means we've been chasing a prototype.
–真实的却落入了这班人手中 –没错
- And these guys have the real one? - Yeah.
我们被赛琳娜耍了
Serena played us for fools.
她背叛了我们
Betrayed us.
这不关系到赛琳娜 这是一场战争…
This isn't about Serena. This is war. And either
我们今天要是不制止他 明天世界就会被毁灭
we stop it today, or we watch the world burn tomorrow.
- 我们得以大事为重 - 对
- Can't lose focus on that. - Yeah.
你到哪去了 去寻欢作乐
Where you been? You stop off for the old rub-and-tug?
你母亲问候你
Your mom says hi.
你放置了追踪器 没被人发现
Tracker on board? Nobody saw you?
–我一直都来去无踪 –很好
- Nobody ever sees me, boss. - Good.
这些官员操控着 所有在空中的卫星
Now, these suits control every spy satellite in the sky.
但这七员有多常机会 同时聚集在一个房间内
But how often do these seven men all sit in the same room together?
几乎没有过
Almost never.
若需要视网膜扫描…
And if you needed retinal scans,
全世界握拳人士的 手机数据转储 生物识别…
cell phone data dumps, biometrics of all the superpowers in the world,
你会锁定谁
who would you target?
该死的
Shit.
有谁握有聚集 那类资讯的权利
Who has that kind of power to actually set that in motion?
你怀疑错人了 是我来找你的 记得吗
You're pissing up the wrong tree, Cage. I came looking for you, remember?
嘿 混蛋 我们惹麻烦了
Yo, asshole. We gonna have problems?
没事 你的旅程还好吗
No problem. How was your trip?
我不过是做做算术罢了
I'm just doing the math.
是吗 何种算术
Yeah? What math?
空气速度除以距离
Air velocity divided by distance.
所以当我把你塞入马桶时 搜寻队伍会知道…
So, when I stuff you down the toilet, search and rescue will know where
得在中国和北韩之间 找到你
to find you between China and North Korea.
继续胡扯吧 小人物
Keep talking shit, little man.
切记你说的话 特种部队士兵
Hold that thought, G.l. Joe.
倒转
Roll it back.
多一些
A little more.
再多一些
More.
停止
A little more. Stop.
当翔撞破玻璃时…
Okay, when Xiang broke the window,
只有他临危不乱
he's the only one that didn't flinch.
替我接通总统
I need the President on the phone...
你知道那是清除不了的吗 我得把整个银幕换掉
That's not gonna come off, you know that, right? I'll have to replace the goddamn screen.
我早说过了 中央情报局局长想要毁灭世界
I've been saying the director of the CIA has been trying to destroy the world for years.
我们被全权委任 拘捕这个混蛋
Okay, we have carte blanche to track this son of a bitch down.
你们有谁知道该如何着手
Do any of you know how to do it?
用回我和翔在纽约找出 潘多拉盒子的方法
The same way Xiang and I found Pandora's Box in New York.
由于卫星不间断的旋转 潘多拉盒子必须重复连接信号
Pandora's Box needs to keep reconnecting itself because the satellites orbit.
请让一让
Excuse me.
我们只需查出 主要信号的来源…
All we need to do is track down the main signal,
就能锁定它在 20英里半径距离内的位置
and then we can approximate its location within a 20-mile radius.
(密歇根州)
(底特律)
在众多可以隐藏的地方…
Of all the places in the world to lay low,
这疯子竟然选择了底特律
this fruit loop chooses Detroit?
(密歇根州 底特律)
爆炸事件虽然发生在莫斯科 世界各地却感受到了余震
These blasts did take place in Moscow, but they were felt around the world.
莫斯科这场悲剧的 死亡人数持续增加
Good morning. As feared, the death toll in the Moscow tragedy is rising.
死伤之余…
In addition to the latest deaths..
让我猜想看 世界各国都趁机拆卸间谍程序
Let me guess. Everyone's jumping at the chance to dismantle their spy programs.
不是
No.
全世界没那么聪明 能看穿莫斯科事件是真实的
The world's too stupid to realize that Moscow wasn't a bluff.
极限特工 你们的基地将设在 国家安全局的安全屋
Okay, Triple-X, you will base out of an NSA safe house.
贝姬会通过耳机操控支援 并使信号中断器处于待机状态
Becky will coordinate earbud communications and have the signal disruptor on standby.
当我为了救你一命 而把船撞击上岸…
Nicks, when I crashed the boat up on shore and saved your life...
随你便 兄弟
Yeah, whatever, bro.
你说那次能正式算是 第199的车祸吗
.do you think that counts as crash 199 for me? You know, officially?
正式而言 你是个疯子
Officially, you're deranged.
好极了
Cool.
我们将设置一个三角形 的信号跟踪系统
We'll set up a triangulated signal tracking system around the city.
贝姬一旦锁定他的正确位置 我们就开始行动
And when Becky locks in his exact location, we make our move.
那你呢 你是如何参与的
What about you? How did you get roped into all this?
我在摩天大楼上涂鸦 被判服刑一年监狱
I tagged a skyscraper and got a year in jail for it.
监狱
Jail?
太极端了
Seems excessive.
那涂鸦长达三十楼层高
The tag was 30 stories tall.
在网上的视频点阅率高达两百万
Two million hits on YouTube.
我也只服刑了一半时间
And I served only half the sentence.
让我猜想 吉本斯来拯救了你
Let me guess. Gibbons to the rescue.
他说像我这般野心 不适合被关在任何笼子里
Yup. He said a lion like me doesn't belong in any kind of cage.
我在离开国家安全局后纹上的
I got mine after I left the NSA.
–你手腕上的呢 –在伦敦
- What about that one on your wrist? - London.
2009年 我成功登上千禧之轮
2009. I climbed the Millennium Wheel.
光着身子
Naked.
–光着 –没错
- Naked? - Yeah.
高中
High school.
不
No!
我们都有过不堪回首的往事
We all have our embarrassing moments.
那个性感的呢
What about that sexy one?
这个 浴火凤凰
This? Phoenix out of the ashes.
我在墨西哥的一张椅子上 花了十八小时完成
Eighteen hours in a chair in Mexico.
我灌下了和我体重相等 的龙舌兰酒才能撑下去
I drank my bodyweight in tequila to get through it.
这也是最具意义的
It's the most important one, actually.
我是在那时候 决定要与世界为伍…
It's when I decided to change the world instead of
而非对抗一切
rage against it.
我们找到他了 也查出潘多拉盒子的位置
We found him. We found Pandora's Box.
桑德 有收到吗
Xander, do you copy?
收到 派上泰尼森
We're here. Okay, send Tennyson.
404号东国会街 他在顶楼
Looks like East 404 Congress Street. He's on the top floor.
(选择卫星)
我接收到潘多拉盒子有动静…
I'm showing activity in Pandora's Box. I can jam the signal,
我只能暂时制止信号几分钟时间 你们动作要快
but only for a few minutes, so hurry.
你们得赶紧抵达 将他压制
You've got to get there fast and take this guy down.
我们得先找到他
Not if we find him first.
红灯 红灯
Red light! Red light! Red light!
交通信号是石油机构发明来 浪费燃料和增加利润的伎俩
Did you know traffic signals were invented by Big Oil
我如果附和你 你能开慢点吗 小心
If I say yes, will you please just slow down? Look out!
等等
Wait.
你是否得在这一刻 担任婊子角色来警告我
Is this the part where you act the basic bitch and tell me you got your eye on me and that you don't trust me?
解答正确
Welcome to the moment.
每个人都需要后备
Everyone needs backup.
停停 停车
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
泰尼森
Tennyson?
交通大堵塞
Gridlocked.
在这里
There it is.
你若遇上麻烦…
If you run into trouble,
拨打9号
dial nine.
这是吉本斯老旧的紧急后备措施
It's an old Gibbons fail-safe.
你打乱了我的计划 也偷走了我的拍档
You crashed my party! Stole my dance partner.
我也来捣乱你
I'm gonna crash yours.
玩的开心
Have fun.
这不是派对 这是一场竞赛
This ain't a party. This is a race.
–你在做什么 –搭建一个坡道
What the hell you think you're doing? Building a ramp.
快去
Go, go, go!
- 给我下车 下来 - 你要干什么
- Hey! Out of the car! Get out! - What are you doing?
快下车
Let's go!
该死的 他尝试重新连接
Shit. He's trying to reconnect it.
我只能在他选择另一颗卫星前 短暂地阻塞信号
Guys, I can only jam the signal for so long before he chooses another satellite.
你们得赶紧
You have to hurry.
我有一个计划
I have a plan.
等等
Hold on!
"等等"才不是什么计划
"Hold on" ain't no goddamn plan!
不 不 不
No, no, no, no!
你在找人吗
You looking for someone?
第两百次的撞击
That's 200!
(第200次车祸 来自底特律的问候)
来啊
Come on.
不 不 不
No, no, no...
桑德 你必须到达顶楼 他正在启动另一颗卫星
Xander, you gotto getto the top floor. He's trying to engage another satellite.
动作快
Huriy.
小事一桩
Fish in a barrel.
四十五口径 德国自动装填手枪
Forty-five U.S.P.
十二颗圆形弹匣
Twelve round mag.
仅剩五颗子弹
Five left.
三颗
Three.
发生了什么事
What the hell's going on out there?
没子弹了
Empty.
阿黛尔 桑德进屋了 找出目标位置并射击
Adele, Xander's in. Find the target, light him up.
吉本斯深信你一定会返回
Gibbons thought you'd be back.
来当我们需要的英雄角色
To be the hero we needed.
你若是把盒子还给 国家安全局…
You take the box to the NSA,
我们就功亏一篑了
and we're right back to where we started.
这真是令人感伤
This is touching.
吉本斯看到你们两人 携手合作一定会倍感欣慰
Gibbons would be proud to see you two working together.
我不会有事的 桑德
I'm walking out of here, Xander.
你要知道一个秘密吗
You want to know a secret?
你忘了涂抹体香剂
You forgot to put deodorant on?
吉本斯是我杀的 他是个自以为正义的白痴
I killed Gibbons because he was a self-righteous prick.
能瞄准吗
Do you have a shot?
他还以为自己是正义的化身
He thought he had the right to police the world.
阿黛尔 瞄准目标了吗
Adele, do you have eyes on the target?
我转换至热瞄准范围
I'm switching to thermal.
我无论如何 都不会停止引爆卫星…
I was never going to stop downing satellites
你知道为何 因为这世界全是一派胡言
no matter what happened. You know why? Because this world has turned...
拜托告诉我你找到射击点了
Please, please, please tell me you have a shot.
该死的
Damn it.
他提升了屋内的温度 我什么也看不到
He's turned the heat up. I can't see shit.
桑德 我看不见你们的位置 热瞄准范围不管用
X can't see you guys. Thermal's no good.
–是吗 –你的温度太高 我看不见你
- Right? - I've lost you in the heat.
你看不到世界的变化吗
You don't see what's going on in this world?
别激动
Take it easy.
–你打算怎么做 –冷静
- So, what are you gonna do about it? - Easy.
桑德 继续让他说话 我还没找到射击点
X, keep Chatty Cathy talking. I still don't have a shot.
一切都是我们造成的 是吉本斯和你们还有我
We made it that way. People like Gibbons and the two of you. And me.
是我们搞砸的
We made it that way. I mean, come on.
这世界若不被重整 每天活着有什么意义
What's the point of getting up in the morning if you're not gonna reboot the world, right?
冷静下来
Okay. Easy.
外头发生战争了 我们为了生存的战斗
There's a war out there. We're at war for our survival, you don't see it?
成千上万的人死得毫无价值
Millions of people have died for nothing... It's their right.
看样子你又得欠我一命了
Read between the lines.
–我说对了吗 –我对你老实说吧
- Isn't it right? - I'm gonna be honest with you.
一直让我心烦的事…
What's been bugging me this whole time
你牙缝中 夹了一些食物
is you've got something stuck in between your teeth.
–你在胡说什么 –我是认真的
- What the hell are you talking about? - I'm serious.
你怎么了
What the hell's wrong with you?
就在…这个位置
Right there.
完美的射击
Nice shot.
你有迟疑过吗
Was there ever a doubt?
是的 我承认我有
Yeah, I confess, I had my doubts.
这就是抹黑我朋友吉本斯的下场
That's for talking shit about my friend, Gibbons.
翔 跪下
Xiang! Get on your knees! On your knees!
手举起来
Hands! Hands!
快跪下
On your knees, now.
赶上了
Just in time.
当心点 凯奇 你再继续这样会被误认为好人
Watch out, Cage. Keep this up, people might mistake you for one of the good guys.
嘿 政府官员
Hey, suit.
你达到目的了
You got what you wanted.
我们都知道他不是坏人
We both know he's not the bad guy.
那莫斯科一事该怪罪于谁
And who do we blame for Moscow?
活生生的恐怖分子 总好过一个死掉的政府官员
Better a living terrorist than a dead company man.
你明白我说什么了
You see what I'm saying?
回到机上 二十分钟后起飞
Let's go. Back on the plane. lwantwheels up in 20.
走吧
Let's go, boys.
我们夺回了潘多拉魔盒
We recovered Pandora's Box.
他们会派来一组押解小队 来接送你们
They're gonna send an extraction team to pick you guys up.
但是翔被他们逮捕了
But they're taking Xiang.
赛琳娜…
And, Serena,
若收不到我的答复 切记 拨打9号
if you don't hear from me, remember, dial nine.
极限特工不会丢下彼此
Xtakes care of its own.
你把盒子还给玛克了 对吗
You gave it back to Marke, didn't you?
这地方真不错 宽敞又昂贵
Nice place. Spacious. Expensive.
闭嘴
Shut up.
谢谢你 长官
Thank you, sir.
是的 少量的死伤人数…
Yes, minimal casualties. Triple-X performed
极限特工的表现 超越了合理的范围
beyond any reasonable measure of expectation.
让我猜想
Let me guess.
那通电话是要 邀约我到总统府
That was my invite to the Oval Office.
在十分钟前 极限特工计划正式被瓦解了
As of 10 minutes ago, the Triple-X program was officially shuttered.
所有特工将从记录档案中删除 并轨列为国家的敌人
All active agents are to be erased from record and considered enemies of the state.
拿枪对准我 从来都不是好办法
It's just never a good idea to point a gun at me.
国家安全局的押解小队 通常都全副武装吗
Hey, are NSA extraction teams normally armed like they're invading Fallujah?
通常不会 看守好这些男孩
No, generally not. Watch the boys.
该死的
Shit.
噢 天哪 有麻烦了是不是
God, it's happening, isn't it?
他们即将展开枪战 对吗
They're gonna start shooting at us, aren't they?
–动作快 –快走
- Come on! - Clear out, let's go!
是时候上场了
It's showtime.
我们现在同属一队了
I guess we're on the same team now.
给我一支枪
Give me one.
你知道我的风格 只要把我瞄准对的方向就行了
You know me. Wind me up, point me in the right direction.
大家走吧
Come on, let's go!
情况变得严重了 是该这个样子吗
This shit is getting real, isn't it? Is this what happens when shit gets real?
我们该怎么做
What do we do?
躲开子弹
Just be where the bullets aren't.
很遗憾的 恐怖份子再度启动潘多拉盒子…
Sadly, the terrorist activated Pandora's Box
但我们无法阻止他
one last time before we could stop him.
你和整个团队在仪器爆炸时 全军覆没
You and your entire team were lost in the blast along with the device itself.
这世界若是认为 潘多拉魔盒被毁灭了…
If the world thinks Pandora's Box is gone,
就无法得知 我们正用来监督他们
then they won't know we're using it to spy on them.
你不过是另一个暴君
You're just another tyrant.
不 是爱国者
No. Patriot.
让我来教育你这其中的分别
Let me educate you on the difference.
桑德
Xander!
听说死亡是最终的历险记 凯奇
They say it's the last great adventure, Cage.
记得给我们寄明信片
Be sure and send a postcard.
–发动引擎 –出发
- Engines hot! - Let's go!
桑德
Xander!
桑德·凯奇
Xander Cage!
–快走 –分散
- Go, go! - Everybody, fan out!
找掩护 快
Find cover! Move!
过去那里
Get behind there!
快找掩护
There, take cover!
真刺激
What a rush.
该死的 贝姬 这防弹背心真了得
Damn, Becky, that's some body armor.
嘿 都说了你这人没礼貌
Hey. I told you you got no manners.
你母亲没教会你 要拉好拉链吗
Did your mother ever teach you howto zip up your pants?
怎样
Well?
赛琳娜
Serena.
我们现在正忙着
We're a bit busy now!
玛克掌握了潘多拉魔盒 她即将在你们上方引爆卫星
Marke's got Pandora's Box. She's gonna drop a satellite on top of you.
她即将对我们引爆卫星
She's gonna drop a satellite on us!
我若把信号阻塞就引爆不了
Not if I jam the signal!
我需要电源
I need a power source!
快去
Go!
我独自一人过去吗
Over there? By myself?
快
Go!
掩护我
Cover me!
快散开
Fan out!
快 快
Go, go!
快过去
Hurry up, over there!
我来应付下侧的攻势
I go low.
我负责上方
Ill go high.
看看是否能找到 那个特种部队士兵
See if I can't find G.I. Joe.
你有接收到干扰信号吗
Are you getting this interference?
该死的
Shit.
把他们干掉 快
Take'em out, now!
每个人都需要后备 对吗
Everyone needs backup, right?
我想是的
Yeah, I guess.
我们开始吧
Let's do this.
尼克斯
Nicks!
–我想到一个计划 –不
- I've got a plan! - No!
不
No, no, no!
听好了 从现在开始 我来策划 你来执行
Listen! From now on, I make the plans, you execute!
该死的
Shit.
天啊 这太棒了
Oh, my God, this is fucking awesome!
怎么了 不反驳吗
What's wrong, hotshot? No witty comeback?
我刚刚算出了 算术的解答
I just finally figured out that math problem.
我得把你冲下马桶两次
It's gonna take two flushes.
上 上
Go, go, go!
数量太多了 我们走吧
Shit. Way too many. Let's get out of here.
跟我们走
Get back! Come on!
妈的
Shit!
我会死掉的
Oh, my, God, I'm gonna die.
快走
Move!
往前
Push forward!
我们只剩这些了
This is all we've got.
拿下他们
Pin'em! Pin'em down!
我没子弹了 你们有吗
Damn! I'm out of bullets. You got any?
什么也没剩
No. Nothing.
我也是
I'm empty.
我们数到三就出动
We go on three.
你好啊
Wassu p?
石头剪刀布… 手榴弹发射器
Rock, paper, scissor, grenade launcher.
达瑞斯·斯通
Darius Stone.
(达瑞斯·斯通 2005年加入极限特工)
(前美国海军军官)
(花了11年时间 等待有人拨打9号)
2005年加入极限特工
Triple-X since 2005.
谢谢你的协助
Thanks for the assist.
极限特工不会丢下彼此
X takes care of its own.
开什么玩笑
You got to be kidding.
(选择卫星)
我们失败了
We failed.
玛克启动了卫星 现在正朝着我们的方向
Xander, Marke activated the satellite and it's headed right for us.
我要像神风敢死队 迎面对抗
I'm gonna have to take it out kamikaze style.
不 那是自杀式袭击 没人能够撑过那种降落距离
Don't do it. It's suicide. Nobody could survive that fall.
让尼克斯备好摄像机
Tell Nicks to have that camera ready.
低轨道自由落体 没有滑槽和大烟花
Low-orbit freefall, no chute and big fireworks.
听说死亡是最终的历险记
They say it's the last great adventure.
记得给我们寄明信片
Be sure to send a postcard.
我是为了这种刺激而活的
I live forthis shit.
该死的
Shit.
尼克斯…
Nicks,
希望你有拍摄下来
I hope you got that on camera!
若没拍到就不算数
If it ain't on video, it didn't happen!
好极了 兄弟 这玩意足以登上名人堂了
Yeah. Hall of Fame shit right here, bro.
–你知道我也能做到 对吗 –胡扯
You know I could've done that, right?
- 省省吧你 - 闭嘴
- Bullshit. - Shut up.
玛克怎么了
What happened to Marke?
她也许摔死了
The ground broke her fall.
还不相信好人
Still don't believe in good guys?
你若是有点使坏 也没关系
It's okay if you're a little bad.
要多坏
How bad?
那个降落…
Now, that right there,
真是超凡的入场
that was a hell of an entrance.
那台车子真是超绝
That's a hell of a car.
吉本斯要我看守好
Yeah. Gibbons told me to keep an eye on it.
他说我到时候 就会明白了
He said I'd know why when I need to know why.
我现在总算明白
Now I know why.
和当年一样 原封不动
It's exactly the way I left it.
我有开出去赴约过
Itook iton adateortwo.
极限特工不会丢下彼此
X takes care of its own.
所以你才会及时出现
That's why I figured you'd come through.
能够跟传奇人物桑德·凯奇 一同共事
To get a chance to work with the legendary Xander Cage?
要到何处报名
Where do I sign up?
你知道自己杠上了 不好惹的家伙
You know, you done pissed on the wrong damn picnic.
我们会被全世界通缉
The whole world gonna be looking for us.
我还是会做出同样的选择
I wouldn't have it any other way.
我们用奥古斯最爱的歌 来做完结吧
We thought we'd end with Augustus' favorite song.
哇 这套把戏真了不起
That's an impressive trick.
干嘛
What?
只有你一人 懂得如何装死
Think you're the only one who knows how to play dead?
上当了吧
Gotcha.
参加自己的葬礼 那种感觉真离奇
This is some pretty surreal shit, being at your own funeral.
我心中想着
∮And I think to myself∮
这世界的确可以很美好
∮What a wonderful World∮
我 真是爱死这首歌了
I love that song.
我们若不做那么多坏事…
And it could be a wonderful world,
这世界的确可以很美好
if we just stopped doing bad shit to it.
你若想要我重出江湖 大可以开口
If you wanted me out of retirement, you could've just asked me.
你一向来不会动心于 微不足道的动机
You always responded to less subtle motivation.
现在要做什么
Now what?
你继续当这世界 真正需要的反叛角色吧
You keep being the rebel the world doesn't know it needs.
看守好政府官员 打击内奸
Watch the watchers. Fight the enemy within.
那太复杂了
Damn, that's so complicated.
是吗
Really?
让我为你简化
Let me simplify it for you.
当个了不起的人物
Kick some ass.
赢取女孩的欢心
Get the girl.
途中尽量显得潇洒
And tryto look dope while you're doing it.
你懂得如何 "潇洒"对吗
You can do "dope," can't you?
你肯定行的
Sure you can.
小内马尔 我们走吧
Junior, let's bounce!
回头见 桑德
I'll see you later, X.
这绝对行
I can definitely make that work.
我们开始吧
Let's do this.
我被你耍了
You got me.
骗到你了
Gotcha.
我是玩家 不是士兵
I'm not a soldier, I'm a bailer.
回头见 桑德
I'll see you later, X.
你肯定行的
Sure you can.
再见
Bye-bye.